https://settle4cash.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyAt Settle4Cash, accessible from https://settle4cash.com, one of our
main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy
document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by
Settle4Cash and how we use it.If you have additional questions or require more information about
our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at
info@settle4cash.comLog FilesSettle4Cash follows a standard procedure of using log files. These
files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do
this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information
collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser
type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp,
referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not
linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose
of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site,
tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic
information.Cookies and Web BeaconsLike any other website, Settle4Cash uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are
used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the
pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The
information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our
web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other
information.Privacy PoliciesYou may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the
advertising partners of Settle4Cash. Our Privacy Policy was created with
the help of the Privacy Policy Generator.Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies,
JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective
advertisements and links that appear on Settle4Cash, which are sent
directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address
when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the
effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the
advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.Note that Settle4Cash has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.Third Party Privacy PoliciesSettle4Cash’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or
websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy
Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information.
It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of
certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies
and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser
options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with
specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective
websites. What Are Cookies?Children’s InformationAnother part of our priority is adding protection for children while
using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe,
participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.Settle4Cash does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable
Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your
child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly
encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts
to promptly remove such information from our records.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is
valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that
they shared and/or collect in Settle4Cash. This policy is not applicable
to any information collected offline or via channels other than this
website.ConsentBy using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
